Guide to the Frank Logue Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- B-1 bomber (Box 31)
- Betterment fund (Box 31)
- Berger Brothers Company (Box 31)
- Bicentennial Commission (New Haven) (Box 31)
- (Bicentennial) British Invasion (Box 31)
- Black clergy (Box 31)
- Black Coalition of Greater New Haven, Inc. (Box 31)
- State of the Black Community (Box 31)
- Black Democratic Club of New Haven (Box 31)
- Black history (Box 31)
- Black New Haven (Box 31)
- Black Women for Justice (Box 31)
- Black Women (Box 31)
- Blinded Veterans Center (Box 31)
- Block Associations
  - Block Association-Church Street South (Box 31)
  - Block Associations (Box 31)
  - Block Association-Hallock Street (Box 31)
  - Block Association-Sylvan Avenue (Box 31)
  - Block Association-Whalley Avenue (Box 31)
- Blue Cross-Blue Shield (Box 31)
- Brotherhood (Box 31)
- Bridgeport-television (Box 31)
- Brandford Motors, Inc. (Box 31)
- Budgeting-zero base (Box 31)
- Business (Box 31)
- C (Box 31)
- C (Box 31)
- Center for Advocacy, Research & Planning, Inc., 1979 (Box 31)
- Central Avenue, Little League field (Box 31)
- Cerebral Palsy Telethon (Box 31)
- Chamber of Commerce (Box 31)
- Chamber of Commerce (Box 31)
- Chamber of Commerce-Retail Council (Box 31)
- Chamber Retailers meeting (Box 31)
- Chapel Street merchants (Box 31)
- Children in Crisis, Inc., miscellaneous (Box 31)
- Children's Museum (Box 31)
- Christian outreach lifeline (Box 31)
- Church Street South (Box 31)
- City Insurance (Box 31)
- Citizens' Assembly (Box 31)
- Cliford W. Beers Guidance Clinic (Box 31)
- Closed Corporation (Box 31)
- Coalition of Northeast Munici (Box 31)
- Community Action Agency (CAA) (Box 31)
- Community Action Agency (Box 31)
- Community Action Agency (CAA) (Box 31)
- Community based organizations (Box 31)
- United States Community Services Administration (Box 31)
- Conferences (Box 31)
- Conferences (Box 31)
- Conference of Democratic Mayors, National (Box 31)
- Connecticut Alcohol and Drug Abuse Council (Box 31)
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association (Box 31)
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association (CBIA) Dorado Beach, 1979 March (Box 31)
- Connecticut Basketball Association (Box 31)
- Connecticut Education Association (Box 31)
- Connecticut Limosine Service (Box 31)
- Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority (Box 31)
- Conrail (Box 31)
- Construction Contractor's Assistance Center Report (Box 31)
- Construction Contractor's Assistance Center (Box 31)
- Cooperative consumers of New Haven, Inc. (Box 31)
- Council on Environmental Quality (Box 31)
- Counseling (Box 31)
- Crime regarding Community Crime Prevention Council, 1979 November (Box 31)
- Crime regarding task force, 1979 January (Box 31)
- Criminal Justice Supervisory Board (Box 31)
- Anti-Crime Consortium (Box 31)
- Crime problems (Box 31)
- Juvenile detention facility (Box 31)
- Juvenile detention center on Whalley Avenue (Box 31)
- Crime (Box 32)
- Criminal justice-action (Box 32)
- D (Box 32)
- Dilieto, Biagio (Box 32)
- New Democratic Club (Box 32)
- Democratic National Committee (Box 32)
- Democratic Convention (Box 32)
- Democratic State Central Committee (Box 32)
- Democratic Party (Box 32)
- State Democratic platform (Box 32)
- 1981-"Year of the Disabled" (Box 32)
- Decisions Inc. (Box 32)
- Dixwell Community House (Box 32)
- Dixwell Opposes Alcohol, Inc. (Box 32)
- Downtown Council (Box 32)
- E (Box 32)
- E (Box 32)
- East Haven (Box 32)
- Earthquake reliefs (Box 32)
- ELKS convention (Box 32)
- Eli Whitney Technical School (Box 32)
- Planning and Energy Policy, Department (Box 32)
- Solar Energy (Box 32)
- Connecticut Energy Savings (Box 32)
- Energy (Box 32)
- Energy (Box 32)
- Environment (Box 32)
- Ethnic groups-phone numbers (Box 32)
- E.R.A. (Box 32)
- F (Box 32)
- Fact sheet (Box 32)
- Fair Haven Clinic (Box 32)
- Fair Haven Parents Ministry Inc. (Box 32)
- Federal Paper Board (Box 32)
- Federal Regional Council of New England (Box 32)
- Financial Emergencies-report (Box 32)
- City Financial Emergencies (Box 32)
- Forbes Avenue Businessmens Association Tomlinson Bridge (Box 32)
- G (Box 32)
- G (Box 32)
- Goals for New Haven (Box 32)
- Grand Avenue (Box 32)
- Greater New Haven Business and Professional Men's Association (Box 32)
- Greater New Haven Property Owners Association (Box 32)
- Guida, Bartholomew (Box 32)
- Guida, Bartholomew (Box 32)
- Guida, Administration (Box 32)
- H (Box 32)
- H (Box 32)
- Hamden (Box 32)
- Hartford (Box 32)
- Hatch Act (Box 32)
- Hill Health Center (Box 32)
- Hilgenhurst Report (Box 32)
- Hill Coalition (Box 32)
- Hispanic (Box 32)
- Mid-Chapel Merchants Coop (Box 32)
- N (Box 32)
- NAACP (Box 32)
- NCPSI (Box 32)
- National Captive Nations Committee (Box 32)
- National Institute of Public Management (Box 32)
- National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs (Box 32)
- National Conference of Democratic Mayors (Box 32)
- National Education Association (Box 32)
- National Democratic Convetion (Box 32)
- National Nursing Home Week (Box 32)
- Neighborhood Housing, Inc. (Box 32)
- Neighborhood Housing Services, Inc., 1979 (Box 32)
- "A New America," "A New City Hall," "The New Haven Register" (Box 32)
- New City Hall (Box 32)
- New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 32)
- New Haven Blueprint (Box 32)
- New Haven-general (Box 32)
- New Haven Boy's Club (Box 32)
- New Haven Scholarship Fund, Inc. (Box 32)
- P (Box 33)
- P (Box 33)
- Parent Aide (Box 33)
- Parents/Teachers Association (Box 33)
- Patrolmen's and Firemen's Association (Box 33)
- Peace Movement (Box 33)
- Pornography (Box 33)
- Powder House Day (Box 33)
- Presidential candidate (Box 33)
- Presidential candidate (Box 33)
- Proc's Music Club (Box 33)
- Professional Development Association (Box 33)
- Vice-Presidential selection (Box 33)
- Proposition 13 (Box 33)
- Public Employee Union (Box 33)
- Public Technology, Inc. (Box 33)
- Public Housing Site Selection Task Force (Box 33)
- Public Utilities (Box 33)
- No. GP-79-032 for Public and Private Utilities in New England (Box 33)
- Public Works Employment Act, 1976 (Box 33)
- Publications (Box 33)
- International Management Week, 3rd week in January (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous (Box 33)
- Ukrainian Independence Day 1/22 (Box 33)
- Q (Box 33)
- Q (Box 33)
- Queen Elizabeth (Box 33)
- Quinnipiac Club (Box 33)
- Quinnipiac River (Box 33)
- R (Box 33)
- New Haven Ravens Football (Box 33)
- Realtors of Greater New Haven (Box 33)
- Recall (Box 33)
- Red Cross (Box 33)
- Redistricting Commission (Box 33)
- References (Box 33)
- Register, New Haven (Box 33)
- Regional Mental Health Center (Box 33)
- Regional Rehabilitation Institute (Box 33)
- Rehabilitation Center (Box 33)
- Relay Run (Box 33)
- Republicans (Box 33)
- Edward J. Cosgrove, 1976 January 7 (Box 33)
- Resumes-secretarial (Box 33)
- Resumes-city manager (Box 33)
- Resumes (2) (Box 33)
- Resumes (3) (Box 33)
- Resumes (4) (Box 33)
- Resumes (5) (Box 33)
- Resumes (6) (Box 33)
- Resumes (7) (Box 33)
- Resumes (8) (Box 33)
- Resumes (9) (Box 33)
- Resumes (10) (Box 33)
- Resumes (Box 33)
- Revenue sharing (Box 33)
- Roadrace (Box 33)
- Roberto Clemente Humanitarian Award (Box 33)
- S (Box 34)
- S (Box 34)
- Sail New Haven, Sail New Haven (Box 34)
- Salvation Army (Box 34)
- Schiavone (Box 34)
- Sewer use service charge (Box 34)
- Economic Development-Sheraton Park Plaza (Box 34)
- Sister Cities International (Box 34)
- Sierra Club (Box 34)
- Smoking (Box 34)
- Soccer Club (Box 34)
- South Central Agency on Aging (Box 34)
- South Central Community College Day Care Training Center (Box 34)
- South Central Community College regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 34)
- Southern Connecticut State College (Box 34)
- South Bronx-Ed.Logue (Box 34)
- Spanish Cultural Association, Inc. (Box 34)
- Staff retreat (Box 34)
- St. Andrew's Apostle Society (Box 34)
- State politics (Box 34)
- State Technical College (Box 34)
- J.P. Stevens (Box 34)
- John G. Stevens Insurance Agency (Box 34)
- Sunday Blue Laws (Box 34)
- T (Box 34)
- T (Box 34)
- Taft hotel (Box 34)
- Telephone log (Box 34)
- Temple Beth El (Box 34)
- Terminal Taxi Company (Box 34)
- Texas Gulf (Box 34)
- Torah Academy (Box 34)
- Tower One (Box 34)
- Travel agency (Box 34)
- U (Box 34)
- U (Box 34)
- Unions (Box 34)
- United Nations (Box 34)
- United Nations Day, 1978 October 24 (Box 34)
- United Negro College Fund (Box 34)
- United States Savings Bond (Box 34)
- United Way (Box 34)
- University of New Haven (Box 34)
- Urban Development Action Grant, 1979 (Box 34)
- Urban homesteading (Box 34)
- Urban League (Box 34)
- Urban planning and policy (Box 34)
- Urban legislation (Box 34)
- Urban reinvestment (Box 34)
- V (Box 34)
- V (Box 34)
- Veterans of World War I (Box 34)
- Veterans program-City of New Haven (Box 34)
- New Haven Veterans (Box 34)
- Visiting Nurse Association of New Haven (Box 34)
- Volunteers (Box 34)
- W (Box 34)
- W (Box 34)
- Waldbaums (Box 34)
- Walk Against Hunger-New Haven (Box 34)
- Whalley Avenue Businessmen (Box 34)
- Whalley Avenue Supermarket (Box 34)
- NOW-National Organization for Women (Box 34)
- Information Counseling Service for Women (Box 34)
- Women in leadership (Box 34)
- Women in education (Box 34)
- New Haven Women's Liberation Center (Box 34)
- Women Voters League of (Box 34)
- Women workers (Box 34)
- Women's Employment Rights Clinic (WERC) (Box 34)
- Women (Box 34)
- Women (Box 34)
- Women's Alliance for Political Action (Box 34)
- XYZ (Box 34)
- X (Box 34)
- Y (Box 34)
- Yale
  - Yale University regarding general (Box 34)
  - Yale Biological Safety Advisory Committee-biohazards (Box 34)
  - Biological Advisory Committee (Box 34)
  - Yale-Little League (Box 34)
  - Yale-Medical Center (Box 34)
  - Yale School of Medicine-Urology, Epidemiology, and Physiology (Box 34)
  - Yale-Mellon Gallery (Box 34)
  - Yale-Music (Box 34)
  - Yale New Haven-relations (Box 34)
  - Yale budget, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Yale Community Affairs Office (Box 34)
  - Yale-City of New Haven (Box 34)
  - Yale Political Union (Box 34)
  - Yale University regarding Secretary, Office of (Box 34)
  - Yale-Sterling Scholarships (Box 34)
  - Yale Symphony (Box 34)
  - Yale Union (Box 34)
  - Yale Union (Box 34)
  - Yale-Whiffenpoofs (Box 34)
  - Yale-Whiffenpoofs (Box 34)
- Y.M.C.A. (Box 34)
- Y.M.C.A. (Box 34)
- Y.W.C.A. (Box 34)
- Z (Box 34)
- Department of Education Budget Request, 1976-1977 (Box 35)
- Mayor Frank Logue (Box 35)
- Education (Box 35)
- Board of Education (Box 35)
- Board of Education Teacher's Strike, 1975 (Box 35)
- Historic Preservation (Box 35)
- Neighborhood Business Revitalization Program (Box 35)
- Home Maintenance Corporation (Box 35)
- State Historic Preservation (Box 35)
- Connecticut Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 35)
- Jail, New Haven County Whalley Avenue (Box 35)
- Save City Hall (Box 35)
- Holocaust
  - Holocaust Memorial regarding correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 35)
  - Holocaust Memorial regarding documents and reports (Box 35)
  - Holocaust, President's Commission on the regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Holocaust, President's Commission on the regarding documents (Box 35)
  - Holocaust, President's Commission on the regarding minutes of meetings (Box 35)
- Hospice (Box 35)
- Humanities (Box 35)
- Human Development's Transportation Demonstration Program (Box 35)
- I (Box 35)
- I (Box 35)
- Intergovernmental programs (Box 35)
- Intergovernmental Personnel programs (Box 35)
- Internships (Box 35)
- International City Management Association (Box 35)
- Internship (Box 35)
- Interstate Industrial Supplies (Box 35)
- Israel (Box 35)
- Israel Awareness Day (Box 35)
- International Institute of Public Management (Box 36)
- Italy (Box 36)
- Italy-American Civil Rights League (Box 36)
- Irish (Box 36)
- Arky, Freed, Stearns, Watson & Greer-private law firms (Box 36)
- J (Box 36)
- J (Box 36)
- Jackson Papers (Box 36)
- New Haven Jaycees (Box 36)
- Jaycees Housing Corporation (Box 36)
- Jewish Community Council (Box 36)
- Jewish Federation, New Haven (Box 36)
- Jewish Historical Society, New Haven (Box 36)
- Jewish Home for the Aged (Box 36)
- Journal Courier (Box 36)
- Junior Olympics (Box 36)
- Juvenile (Box 36)
- Juvenile Court (Box 36)
- K (Box 36)
- K (Box 36)
- Kentucky Louisville (Box 36)
- Kerr, Chester (Box 36)
- Kohary Park (Box 36)
- Kops-Monahan Travel (Box 36)
- Kramers (Box 36)
- Jeonju City, Korea (Box 36)
- Kresge Foundation (Box 36)
- L (Box 36)
- Landlords (Box 36)
- L (Box 36)
- League of Women Voters (Box 36)
- Lee, Richard C. (Box 36)
- Legislation (Box 36)
- Legislature (Box 36)
- Legislature Bulletin (Box 36)
- Legislative Committee (Box 36)
- Lender's Bagel Bakery (Box 36)
- Lincoln Institute of Land Policy (Box 36)
- Liberty Bell (Box 36)
- List (Box 36)
- Ed Logue (Box 36)
- Long Island Sound (Box 36)
- Long Wharf (Box 36)
- Long Wharf Harborside Park (Box 36)
- M (Box 36)
- M (Box 36)
- Macy's (Box 36)
- Malls (Box 36)
- Management consultant (Box 36)
- Management Employees Union (Box 36)
- Management training (Box 36)
- Mc (Box 36)
- LEAA-USFA Arson Conference (Box 36A)
- LEAA grant application (Box 36A)
- Legal Services Advisory Council (Box 36A)
- Legal Assistance Association (LAA) (Box 36A)
- Legal Enforcement Assistance Association (LEAA) (Box 36A)
- Regional Council of Elected Officials (1) (Box 36A)
- South Central CSJB-Project Heavy (Box 36A)
- Regional Council of Elected Officials (3) RCEO (Box 36A)
- South Central Planning Unit (Box 36A)
- South Central CSJB-minutes (Box 36A)
- South Central CSJB-grant action/application (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Justice Supervisory (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Justice Supervisory Board regarding CJSB grant action, 1979 (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Supervisory Board (CJSB ) (1) (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Supervisory Board (CJSB ) (2) (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Justice Supervisory Board (3) (Box 36A)
- South Central Criminal Justice Supervisory Board (CJSB ) (5) (Box 36A)
- RCEO-September 27, 1978, 12:00 Valle's Restaurant, West Haven, 1978 September 27 (Box 37)
- South Central Connecticut Region (Box 37)
- South Central Health Systems (Box 37)
- South Central Health Systems Agency (Box 37)
- South Central Regional Emergency Medical Communications System C-Med (2) (Box 37)
- South Central Transportation Plan (Box 37)
- CPI Board of Directors (Box 37)
- CPI (Box 37)
- CPI (Box 37)
- CPI, status of programs (Box 37)
- Management, CPI Board of Directors (Box 37)
- P.D. (Box 37)
- CPI (Box 37)
- Connecticut Conference of Municipalities (CCM)
  - Correspondence (Box 38)
  - Personnel (Box 38)
  - Documents and reports (Box 38)
  - Energy Task Force (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee regarding correspondence (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee regarding meeting materials (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee regarding minutes (Box 38)
  - Legislative Committee regarding correspondence (Box 38)
  - Legislative Committee regarding meeting materials (Box 38)
  - Legislative Committee regarding minutes (Box 38)
  - Nominating Committee regarding correspondence (Box 38)
  - Nominating Committee regarding meeting materials (Box 38)
  - Nominating Committee regarding minutes (Box 38)
  - Meeting, February 28, 1978, 1978 February 28 (Box 38)
  - Tax reform (Box 38)
  - Federal management (Box 38)
  - Education finance reform (Box 38)
  - Urban management (Box 38)
- Education Finance Reform Committee (Box 38)
- International Institute of Public Management (IIPM) (Box 38)
- International Institute of Public Management (IIPM), 1979 (Box 38)
- National Institute of Public Management (NIPM) (Box 38)
- National League of Cities (NLC)
  - National League of Cities (NLC) (Box 38)
  - Urban problems "State of the Cities"-report (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-program on urban economic policy (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-Public Safety Steering Committee (1) (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-Public Safety Steering Committee (2) (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-State and local government, task force (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-waste disposal (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC), 1976 November 28-December 1 (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC) (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-general correspondence (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-humanities (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC) (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-city legislators (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-regarding Congress of Cities, 1979 November (Box 38)
  - National League of Cities (NLC)-Public Safety Steering Committee (3) (Box 38)
- National Urban Fellows (NUF)
- National Urban Fellows (NUF) (Box 39)
- National Urban Fellows (NUF) (Box 39)
- National Urban Fellows (NUF) (Box 39)
- National Urban Fellows (NUF)-Board of Directors (Box 39)
- United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM) (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-advisory board (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-labor and management relations (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Resolution Committee (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Arts Standing Committee (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Commission on Urban Growth (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-National Defense Policy (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-general (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-National Defense Policy (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-National Endowment for Humanities (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Public Works and Economic Development Act (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-new regional and metropolitan realities (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)/LRMS United States Conference of Mayors (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Urban Transit Aid Program (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-San Francisco, 1976 July (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Sun Valley, 1978 August (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Atlanta, 1978 August (Box 39)
  - St. Louis Congress of Cities NLC Arts Task Force November 27-28 (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Washington, DC, 1979 January (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Pittsburgh, 1979 June (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-maintaining fiscal balance and expanding economic development (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Steering Committee on Growth Management (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-human services (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM) "Man in Washington" (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Nomination Committee (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-urban growth (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)/NLA (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM) (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Equal Rights Amendment (ERA) ratification (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-Chicago-Gunther Address and '77 Resolutions Committee (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-1980 federal budget (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM) regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 39)
  - United States Conference of Mayors (USCM)-housing and community development (Box 39)
- Citizen's Office Hours, 1976 January-1979 August (Box 40)
- Fire department (Box 41)
- Complaints (Box 40)
- Invitations (Box 40)
- Avignon (Box 40)
- Education-superintendent (Box 40)
- Education regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 40)
- Bicentennial (Box 40)
- American Issues (Box 40)
- Schiavone (Box 40)
- Police Crime Victims' Services Unit (Box 40)
- Grants (Box 41)
- Grants (Box 41)
- Mayor correspondence (Box 41)
- Filing (Box 41)